Ending
Nogizaka-kun, it is banana sound from the main purpose. Please do so.
First, let's start with Nogizaka-chan.
Wai-wai-wai. Wai-wai-wai.
Ding-dong.
There it is, ding-dong.
Now, Mr. Himura, please announce what we are going to do today.
Doktaka Self-Quiz Contest!
Let's go.
Please go ahead.
Quizzes are not only about answering the questions, but also about making up questions.
The members will create quiz questions in advance using only their own knowledge.
We were divided into two teams, with Kaki Endo as the leader.
They take turns to answer each other's questions and get 1 point for each correct answer.
Himura, who didn't know the questions, also participated as a respondent.
The quiz was played by three teams in total.
However, at the end of the quiz match, the winner is chosen from among all the questions
The winner of the quiz match
The best quiz by Shitara will be awarded 3 more points.
the quality of the quiz questions also determines the winner of the quiz match
We were locked in a dark room.
Koichi, you told me to make time problems, right?
That's right.
It took a lot longer than expected, and everyone must have had a hard time.
It's quite difficult, isn't it?
That's why...
Those who didn't answer were really just doing their own personal weird quizzes.
The team with the most points wins.
And the team with the most points wins the prize.
A 50,000 yen QUO card.
Don't be so quick to pull that one out.
Teams.
Teams are good enough.
First, Endo of the Endo team will ask a question.
No teammates know the problem, so all teams push the first question as fast as they can.
Let's start with the first question.
What should I put in the Tupperware to get rid of the smell?
Here they come, the Endo team!
Hot water
Boo boo!
No, it's not. Himemaru-san.
Vinegar.
Ah, here it comes.
Salt.
Vinegar.
Salt and.
Oh, here it comes, Himemaru.
Salt and lemon.
No, it's not.
Eight minutes.
Salt water.
Correct!
So that's what it is.
It's salt and water.
I see.
Salt water is fine.
One point for the team, sir.
What's this?
Copper always smells bad.
I told him to put some water and salt in it, cover it and shake it to get rid of the smell.
Did he teach you that?
Yes, I did.
That's why I locked myself in a room... to get it out of my knowledge.
I see. That sounds interesting.
I like it. So that's how we'll do it.
This is fun.
Super fun this
Next, Kaki team Umezawa came up with this quiz
QuestionThe bottoms of small jars of salt and seasonings are jagged, right?
What is the reason for that?
To prevent sedimentation.
No, it's not.
Wait a minute... do you guys get it?
It's jagged here.
Outside.
That's what it looks like.
Like the shichimi and the salt.
They're all jagged.
There's a reason for this.
Yes, there is a reason.
Rubbing the jagged edges together keeps the powder from hardening.
Correct.
How did you know this?
Did you know? I didn't know that was possible.
Did you know that?
No. What is that?
Can you try this one for me?
When it gets stuck down there, you can put it back up like this.
Oh, my God.
You can touch it.
It's true. It's true.
That's true.
Wrong.
It doesn't say that.
I saw this in a book.
I tried it at home, and I thought it was really useful.
Wrong.
Wrong
Ikeda knew it well
Yes.
If it's really this kind of problem, I really think I can get it, can I go get it?
It's okay.
That's frustrating.
It sounds like a good question, but it's not a good question if you can answer it right away.
Yoshida also started with a trivia I know.
When you crack open a raw egg, what is the name of the whitish translucent thing on the yolk?
There it is, here we are, Team Oyster!
Body
Correct answer!
How did you know that?
How did you know? How did I know? Ask me something.
It's a good question, but you answered it right away.
Wow.
And then the other team takes it.
I would have preferred to be taken by my team.
Next, Kaki team Inoue's question...
What is "nikuman"?
It's hard to figure out.
Come on, team Kaki!
I've been waiting for a while. "Nikujiru" is the official name.
What's a steamed bun?
What do you mean?
How did it come about?
The meat rolled around.
It got covered with sand.
It became steamed buns.
No, it didn't.
Mr. Himura.
You want to preserve the delicious meat.
To keep it from spoiling.
It's a kind of preserved food.
No, sir.
Just a little.
A small basket wasn't enough.
There was a package in the first place.
I'll give you a hint... God.
God?
I put the meat in the case as an offering, so I could eat it.
Nice try.
It's a substitute for something.
Yes, it is.
In place of something?
Your heart.
No, it's not.
When someone dies, you offer it as a substitute for their body.
Where's the body now?
Eyes.
Eye
Please answer after you press the button.
The heart of the body, the liver, the kidneys, the heart of the body, the liver, the kidneys, the kidneys
Heart of the body. Liver.
No, no, no, I told you.
You said two of them.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
But in the end, there was no correct answer, and time ran out on this problem.
What was it?
It's an old Chinese story about a man who offered his head to the gods as a provision for the gods.
I heard from a junior high school teacher that it started when they offered something to go in place of it.
I heard from a teacher in junior high school that this is the beginning.
You heard that from a middle school teacher?
That's amazing.
We had a lot of fun, but we never got to the correct answer.
That's fun.
Next is a question from Ikeda.
What is the Korean word for a certain part of meat in yakiniku?
What is the Korean word for "yi"?
If there is someone who knows this...
Ah, here comes the team end!
Puchan
Puchang
Mino.
Mino no, sir.
Thousand pieces
Not even close
Kopchang
What's that you're saying about Kopchang?
Two letters.
Mino.
No, no, no, not Mino.
Not Mino.
I'll give you a hint.
It's like the nickname of a certain member of the Nogizaka group.
Mingo.
Yes, yes, yes...
"Haikita Team Kaki" (Oyster)
Den
Haikita Team Himura
Sun
very likely
San
tsk tsk
Hit it, this hitter's already hit it!
He's gone.
Yayon
No, I'm done!
Yay!
That's right!
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Wait a minute.
It's called Yang.
I heard it's incredibly difficult to process.
I ate it.
Was it good?
It was super delicious.
I'm glad.
Mr. Kimura.
I finally got one.
I guess the bow cutter got the hint.
Bummer.
Nimura also got it right, and the quiz heated up.
Next was Ito's problem
Bananaman brought fruit to the live!
In the basket, there were 3 bananas, 2 grapes, 3 apples, 5 oranges, and 2 pears!
How many fruits are in the basket?
It would be great if you could answer with your reasons too!
Yes, here we go team Karkick!
I can't count.
Here we go.
The answer is four. The reason is there are supposed to be no pears.
Boo. No, sir.
Eight. Eight.
I don't know why. Because it's basket two.
In basket two, there are three bananas, two grapes, three apples.
And five oranges and two pears.
Because that's how many are in Basket 2.
Three plus two plus three makes eight.
Correct.
Very good! Very good!
How did you figure it out so quickly?
It's easy to do.
People often think it's even more difficult than it is.
It's amazing you can answer that riddle so quickly.
You're smart. You got it now.
Next is a riddle by Endo's team, Mukai.
What is the name of the younger sister of Chibimaruko-chan's friend Boutaro?
Tomiko.
What is it?
I was going to say "Tomiko.
But you know it!
That's great!
But I got him to do it...
But the question of Boutaro's real name...
It turned into a guessing contest, and I had to say his name a lot.
It's over.
Taro Tomita
Correct answer
As Boo Taro, I wanted to shoot it.
This is not Boo Taro.
Boutaro would probably know this.
Next, a question from Kaki's favorite cartoon.
When Anpanman's face gets wet or chipped in a fight, he can replace it and regain his strength, but how does Karepanman regain his strength?
He fries it up again.
No, it's not.
No, sir.
Akita Team End
Drink the curry
I'll drink it.
Correct!
Ikeda, this is...
This is...
IkedaYou know this?
I've seen Cee like this in a curry pot.
It's common to see her face up, open her mouth and pull it out of the pot like this.
Wow.
Put it in with your hands.
Ikeda's amazing!
Ikeda's strong
He's so strong
Next is a question from Endo's team Kubo
I was standing in front of a store and they gave me something.
What is it now?
Here comes the team!
A chair
A chair.
No, I'm tired.
Yes, Mr. Himura.
The sun has set.
Correct.
Mysterious question with overwhelming strength!
Mr. Himura, this is great!
Yes, this is great.
I don't know if it's a riddle or not.
I don't know if it's a puzzle or not.
Mr. Imura is very good at this kind of problem.
It's crazy.
I thought "touched" was a strange word.
You're right.
Like giving something away.
"Touched" is a bit of a turn-on, isn't it?
That's amazing.
I'm overwhelmed by the mystery of it all.
I'm catching up.
Nadzu Nadzu is a demand! What's Nakamura's problem?
The word "matinee soiree" is often used on stage.
What is the name of the performance of the time in between?
Wow, this is an early idea shoement!
Matinee soiree
No, sir.
Matisowakan?
Intermission
But after this, no one knew the answer.
And the only thing to do is to look for a word that starts with the initial clue 10.
Here we are, team khakis.
Jurine!
So close!
Oh, no, no, no.
But the closest!
Oh, here it comes!
Jornet.
You were right.
That was strong.
I've been doing this kind of thing for a while.
Next is a problem that Sakaguchi came up with.
What surprised me when I was eating a Japanese confectionery monaka?
Here he is, Mr. Himura!
On the back of my teeth.
I got it all on the back of my teeth.
That's not it.
No, it's not.
Yes, it is.
It's gone.
No, they're not.
It was a monaca.
Rough quiz.
I got it wrong.
Me, too.
No pun intended.
I see.
Fact.
That skin is the same as the one you use to scoop goldfish.
No, it's not.
Hardly.
The skin is made of corn.
Almost, but not quite.
Nice try!
Why did you do that?
North team end
The skin is made of flour.
No, it's not.
Nice try.
I can't imagine what that crust looks like
Yes, team cut.
Nuts?
No, sir.
You've had nuts before.
What? I don't know what they are.
Okay, team end.
Rice.
Oh, my God.
Correct.
Wow!
The skin is made of glutinous rice, not wheat
Wow, I didn't know that.
I didn't know that.
It's glutinous rice.
So this is a surprise.
Yes, it was.
I was trying to go gluten-free, and then I looked at the back.
Oh, it's not wheat.
Wow.
That's a first.
Good question!
The next question is from Ichinose.
First of all, please look at this image.
Please look at the image.
1. a small rabbit
2. rabbit
3. tent
What is in Shiori Kubo's brain?
Inside her brain
Inside Kubo's head
What is it? Oh, did my hand stop?
Akita Team Khaki
Baseball
Is this some kind of a trick question?
I see. Kubo likes baseball.
Yes, sir.
So...
Eggplant?
Suboh.
What do you mean?
I got a no.
No.
I think it's a good idea, don't you?
That's what I'm talking about.
The first one to get in wins.
Mr. Kubo has nothing to do with it.
No and no means no.
Correct.
Yes!
The third tent is correct. Ichinose, please explain.
The one that is in here and has no "no" and "woo" in it. The correct answer is a tent without a "nou" in it.
This is a bit of a mystery, too.
What is this? Did you do a quiz like this in the past?
No, there was nothing in my head at the time, so I thought about it for an hour.
I thought about it for an hour, and this is what I came up with.
Wow!
What do you think?
I'm out of my mind.
Uncle Kimura did a great job and it was a very close game.
Who will win the Nogizaka Quiz Contest?
Next, we have a question from Yumiki.
Is this a service question?
It's a very service question.
Now, please try your best to answer Yumiki's question.
Which animal can be turned into a penguin if you tap it on the head?
Penguin
Correct answer
What's that?
And Kaede Sato answers
A penguin.
What's this problem?
I thought I'd have to write something to finish.
I squeezed and squeezed and squeezed, and after applying various animals, I came up with penguins.
I see.
If Yumiki didn't make this problem, it's already dead.
It's going to be "Gin-Gin"!
What's "Gin-Gin"?
Don't call it "Gin-Gin"!
But it's one point.
Oh no!
Next is a quiz by Kaki Team Iyoki!
It's a quiz about yourself.
Self-quiz
I've been living alone for 3 years and have never run out of dish detergent and ouro detergent in my house
I have never run out of them.
Why is that?
I have a reason.
Yes, team persimmon
I don't wash them.
If that's the answer, I don't understand.
Here we are, team persimmon.
I don't know if I'm overdoing it, but it's kind of a pain to arrange... because your mom secretly adds it without your knowledge.
What?
How can you not see that right away?
Because we're exactly the same.
I'm surprised it's not gone.
I'm surprised it hasn't gone away.
I'm amazed it hasn't gone away.
I didn't know it lasted this long.
You didn't even know about the eboshi itself?
I was on the phone with my mom the other day, and I was talking about how you live alone and have so much.
She said, "My mom is buying it for me.
Wow...
She didn't tell you?
You were exactly the same?
I've been thinking about changing to a new hand soap as soon as possible.
She'd quietly change the detergent and shampoo and leave.
I've always wondered if the APRO stuff would ever go away.
Three years is too long.
That's amazing.
And the next quiz Kawasaki came up with?
I'm going to give my own quiz, but I eat ________ every day without fail.
What the hell is that?
Here comes the team.
Kabayaki-kun
Kabayaki-kun?
No, sir.
Mr. Ohira.
Natto (fermented soybeans)
No, sir.
What is it?
Cafe latte.
Yes, sir.
Oh, yes.
No, sir.
No, no, no, no, no.
I drink one every day.
Mikey and the boys are mendacious.
Pancakes.
Every day?
That's great.
It's the sweet kind.
The sweet kind.
Here comes the team end.
Yogurt.
No, it's not.
Ice cream.
That's right.
That's good, right?
Ice cream.
I always eat ice cream, no matter how cold it is.
Why?
What's wrong with that?
I'm on a mission.
The other day, I was in a parking area with a group of students.
I had goosebumps in short sleeves.
It was freezing.
It was freezing cold and everyone was eating warm food like steamed buns and fried chicken.
It's called his head, isn't it?
Thank you very much.
Eat every day. Every day? I ate it again today.
You haven't missed it since you joined Nogizaka?
Ice cream for breakfast.
Ice cream helps me get up early.
I go to bed thinking I'm going to eat ice cream.
So I don't oversleep.
You wake up very differently from me.
I'm determined. You get up at 6:00 a.m.?
I get mad when there's ice cream.
After this, the Nogizaka quiz contest is over.
Next is a question by Kaki Team Sato.
This is a quiz about myself.
When I was a student, for the first time in my life, I had to talk to the guidance department.
What was the first mistake I made when I was a student that got me into trouble with the guidance department?
Let's go to the team end!
I ate a sample and got in trouble.
Correct answer.
I knew that.
Congratulations!
What's this all about?
The school has a cafeteria.
There are samples of the day's menu on display.
But some of them are the real thing.
I ate some of them and got in trouble.
You mean you ate the real ones?
Yes, sir.
What did you eat?
I had the ham cutlet on top of the curry.
That's great.
The best.
That's the worst.
You had the ham and pork cutlet curry.
That's not good.
You're doing a quiz on yourself.
It's a quiz on yourself, Mr. Nimura...
A self-quiz?
I can't do a quiz on myself.
There's a riddle coming.
I want a mystery.
But what about the next question from Endo?
Here's the question.
This is a quiz for myself.
What do I watch every day before I go to sleep?
What?
Here it is.
The 101st proposal.
Laughter
Candlelight Day
Horror Movie
Too Close to Call
Team End
Mr. Himura
Team Kirky
Errrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrr.
Nightmare
I watch them before I go to bed.
After I go to bed.
Yes, team khakis.
Tiger youtube.
Correct.
That's right.
What's that?
It's a tiger game.
What the hell is that?
What? Endo, really? The one where the guy goes to haunted places?
Yes, there's a channel, and it's scary, but it makes me want to watch it.
But I don't want to watch it before I go to bed because I might have scary dreams or something.
I'm fine. I've already taken a bath, and I'm just going to sleep when I watch it.
What? That's scary.
Let's go back to Yumiki's Ogawa-type stuff.
Himura-san's got caught in the middle.
I caught it.
I really like him.
I love him so much that I laugh when he talks.
Even when he doesn't say anything funny.
Look, look, look.
I love Mr. Himura so much that I call him a psychic.
He's not a psychic.
He's a psychic.
Hiro-san likes psychic videos, so Endo likes Mr. Himura.
What's this?
No, no...
I haven't watched any of your videos.
No, I haven't.
Wait, look!
Look!
Look at it!
Oh, no...
I didn't hear that.
I'm so embarrassed.
Here comes Mr. Himura.
Your legs are long.
No, they're not.
Long legs.
Nogizaka46 36th single to be released
New center will be announced in the next program!
Hi, this is Lilia Ito.
I've recently seen my favorite Conan movie three times.
But three times is not enough for me.
Influenced by that, I'd like to go to Hakodate in Hokkaido to make a pilgrimage to the holy land and eat a lot of delicious food.
I'd like to go to Hakodate in Hokkaido to make a pilgrimage to a holy place and eat a lot of delicious food.
Thank you for subscribing to my channel!
Thank you very much.